Get them all out of here now!
Cops were clearing an
empty lot in an effort
to make our city pretty
in time for the Olympics.
Alton didn't want to leave.
Well. I give you the money.
you just gon' go give it to my moms?
- No. no. it ain't like that.
- Been like that
since I was old enough to know
what the word "deadbeat" meant.
You want some good news?
I moved that key.
Valley is thirsty. amigo.
Sounds like you knew
Alejandro pretty well.
He's my husband.
Been circling for weeks.
Only a matter of time
before they find us.
One was a drug dealer and
the other was a woman.
- and he killer her...
- So you killed him.
I had no choice.
Handguns. assault rifles. submachines.
I only care that you can deliver them
- somewhere outside the country.
- Have a place in mind?
I hear that Panama is
nice this time of year.
If Gabby told you to fuck your mother.
you'd fuck yourmother.
The way she held that gun.
the way she stood...
she's a fucking cop.
Or DEA. but definitely the law.
If she's a cop.
what does that make Pedro?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
The longer I'm here. the more questions
I have to answer when I get back.
We're pulling you. Lorena.
Why would you do that?
- You killed someone.
- In self-defense.
Helped them dispose of the bodies...
I didn't do shit but patch
up that fucking bitch.
Should have arrested them
right then and there.
So that's what we're gonna do now...
arrest the Villanuevas.
Whoever we get after that we get.
You take Lucia off the board now.
all of her contacts get
spooked and scatter.
- including the suppliers.
- We still take a bite
- out of La Fuerza.
- La Fuerza's whack-a-mole.
The real prize here is the
pilot and his partner.
Tony...
We get them.
and we've got a shot at the cartel.
The fucking Colombians.
Cover of "The Times." your ugly face
and 3 tons of cocaine.
You know this isn't just
my decision. right?
You'll have to say I wouldn't listen.
that I refused to come in.
which I'm about to do anyway.
so won't be that big of a stretch.
How much time do you need?
48 hours.
Just enough to get these
assholes in handcuffs.
Then we take the Villanuevas.
and after that I don't care
how the dominoes fall.
Please.
Tony.
Two days?
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
_
This is delicious.
Wow.
From Graves. bottled in 1942.
Even in war. someone is making wine.
I'd like to imagine buxomy French women
squishing grapes between their toes.
There will be a service
fee of 350 per shipment.
Well. it was smart of
you to pour the wine
before you dropped that number on us.
Well. this is in Mexico
City. where the wind blows
a different direction every day.
Noriega has changed everything.
You are buying the backing and security
of the Panamanian government
from top to tail.
Switzerland without the snow.
Yeah. I appreciate what
you're offering us.
that's why we're here.
Now...
if I could guarantee that
this was going to be
an ongoing relationship.
what would you do
to earn my business?
I suppose we could cut the price enough
to make you smile... say 20%?
30% would make me smile more.
I cannot make you smile that much.
You provide assurances with security
and handling of privacy. yeah?
Total.
If anything happens to
any of your shipments
from port to plane. we
will make you whole again.
Whatever it takes.
We're not just silk-glove handling.
We're a peace-of-mind guarantee.
I'm feeling better already.
27% drop on all subsequent shipments.
25.
So nice dealing with
consummate professionals
for a change.
Indeed.
Corner boy's pulling in
5k a week over there
- at Tommy's Burger.
- That's good.
Got me thinkin'...
maybe we should start
using local businesses
in the neighborhood. you know?
Like that check-cash place on 42nd.
People can come in with
they paychecks and leave
with that hard rock.
Why you always trying to
make the shit more visible?
What you mean more visible. man?
This is less pressure on
the hand-to-hand. off us.
We ain't gotta be driving around
doing re-ups all day.
Those places will all want a cut
for taking on the risk.
Lot more than I'm willing to pay out.
Think of something else. man. huh?
That's flashy.
Yeah. all right.
Ey. can I get a Push-Up Pop?
- We closed. mama.
- Oh. then a Choco Taco
or a drumstick with the nuts on top?
- Sorry. we're not open.
- No?
Not even for some of that
rock you got in there?
- Excuse me?
- Gotta give it to you.
shit's pretty smart.
I mean. who's gonna pull
over a ice cream truck?
And I bet it's easier
than slinging on foot. too. huh?
Not sure what you're
talking about. miss.
- but have a nice day. okay?
- I'ma need you
to come out here and talk
to me first. Franklin.
It's about your father.
- Who are you?
- Nia Jones.
What you want with Alton?
The cops are pressing charges
even though they're the ones
who beat the shit out of him.
_
Can't help you.
Well. I checked your mom's place.
Should be checking under overpasses.
You know. for somebody
passed out in the gutter.
No. he's been staying sober.
sticking to his program.
Ain't missed a meeting till today.
- 'Till today. huh?
- Uh-huh.
You just said it.
Shit always ends the same with him.
Maybe this time will be different.
- You're wasting your time.
- Look.
if he's gotta fight this.
I need these forms signed
and in by tomorrow.
He doesn't. they'll
throw his ass in jail.
and a black man with a record.
that's where he'll stay.
Again. Miss Mia Jones...
shit always ends the same with him.
He needs a lawyer. Go
ahead and get him one.
He's your father. You get him a lawyer.
Mr. Ice Cream Man.
I'm gonna keep looking for him.
You hear anything. you
know where to find me.
Have yourself a great day.
You should go home.
After Gabriella comes.
Until then. everything
has to seem normal.
Seem normal?
What is normal?
I remember when my dad found this place.
It felt huge.
He was so excited.
We all were.
I sure fucked this up.
You were right. Oso.
I should have never let Pedro back in.
We can always run.
Yeah. right now.
We'll look guilty.
Start over again. you and me.
Spend the rest of our lives
looking over our shoulders.
I can't live my life that way.
Seem normal.
- Motherfucker.
- Normal.
Hey. I thought we agreed to meet later.
We didn't know when the
shipment was coming in.
Wanted to be here to help.
Sorry. we should have called you.
The white boys cancelled it.
Did they say why?
No. and Gabby's gonna
be here any minute.
It might be better if
you two aren't here.
- We'll stay if you need us.
- No.
If they want us to go. we should go.
Let's go.
You'll call us if you need us. yes?
Of course we will.
Thanks for checking in.
Of course.
- Hey...
- Number four. please.
Hey. uh. you two go on without me.
Gotta see a man about a horse.
Thought you were coming out with us.
Just leave a note with the concierge.
- I'll meet up with you.
- Panama City
is a very dangerous place
to wander around alone.
Don't worry. Matt will protect you.
Elena.
Sorry I'm late.
What's my budget?
400.
New munitions. new suppliers.
new routes. less money?
Look. we are as committed as
ever to winning this war.
This support... is not going anywhere.
You keep telling me what you need.
I'm gonna keep getting it for you.
The doctors in Jinotega
wanted to amputate it.
My leg. too.
Glad we got you to Dallas.
Okay. So. yeah.
that first shipment
should start arriving...
in the next couple weeks.
Our Panamanian friends will
take it to the airstrip
in Camarones. and then
my pilot will pick it up
and whisk it in to you.
This new pilot...
he knows how to fly low and heavy?
Yeah. he's flown dozens
of combat missions.
So did Alejandro.
I never got a chance to tell you. uh...
properly how sorry I was
about what happened.
He was a good man...
and he was a good soldier.
I only hope that I can
live up to his memory.
Keeping your promises would
be a good place to start.
What are they all doing here?
Considering your accusation.
I thought they should be here.
Avoid any confusion.
_ shipment.
Pretty simple. no?
See. that's exactly what I mean.
'cause they say different.
Stomper. Memo. and Stranger
left our place last night
with the money on their
way here to pay you.
They never came back.
Maybe they went to Vegas instead.
Look. all I know is that
we held up our end...
provided the product. and it sold.
Now we want our money.
I don't think they believe you. Niña.
I really don't care what they believe.
- Fucking lying puta.
- Hey. stop.
Everybody fucking stop.
Get the fuck out!
Everybody outside but me and her! Go!
Today. dumbshits!
Cabrón. get the fuck out.
Come on.
Ay...
You said you could keep them in line.
That they'd play ball.
This is fucking bullshit. Gabriella.
You know. I didn't grow up in this life.
My father worked on cars.
My mother at home watched
me and my brothers.
I could have gone that way.
Married a normal man.
been at home with my babies.
Blow my fucking brains out. huh?
When I met Ybarra. I knew. That was it.
And when he went away...
I wasn't scared.
'Cause that's what I wanted...
to be the boss.
That's what you want. too.
You wanna give orders.
You don't wanna take 'em. huh?
I know.
I respect that. I get you.
When I think about the daughter I lost.
what kind of woman she would have been.
I think about you.
Only. I just...
I picture someone a little bit...
fucking smarter. huh?
Oh. yeah.
Gotta be pellets. a wound that big. huh?
Fucking hurts. I know. Whole
shoulder on fire. right?
You gonna tell me the truth or
keep feeding me shit. puta?
They fucking came at us.
- We didn't have a choice.
- Yeah? Well. it don't matter.
I don't make the rules. We
all gotta play by them.
I'm sorry.
- I'll pay you.
- Yeah?
$1/4 million tomorrow.
I'll need 1/4 for each shot-caller
and another for me. That's 1.5. niña.
to buy your life.
- You got that lying around?
- You kill me.
and the connect goes away.
That's okay. I'll get another.
What if I can offer you something
worth more than 1.5?
What?
The recipe.
You cook the crack yourself.
You think you're making money now?
You could have 1.5 coming in a month.
Let's say I was interested.
The Monarcas want your head.
I just need a few days.
I won't be able to hold
them off for long.
You fuck around with me.
it's not just gonna be the end of you.
It's gonna be the end
of every Villanueva
from here to Sinaloa.
the entire bloodline wiped out.
Forever. you understand?
Feel better.
Number 12. Number 12. you're up.
All right. I'm here.
So important it couldn't wait?
We'll give you the vato
who killed your friends.
Where to find him. how to kill him
so nobody knows it was you.
No blowback. no war.
Just revenge.
I can also pay you $1/4 million in cash.
I'm afraid to even ask
what you want in return.
The recipe.
- This is real. Franklin.
- Answer's no.
You didn't even think about it.
I don't need to think about it.
I told you.
I'm willing to make as
much rock as you want...
but I ain't giving up the process.
- Thought you wanted revenge.
- Not at that price.
Have a good night.
Be safe out here.
Hey.
This isn't greed.
We are in trouble. amigo.
Need your help to get out of it.
When you needed ours we were there...
Saved your life.
Maybe it's time to repay us.
I'm grateful to you for that.
Won't never forget it.
But this is the one thing
I can't do for you. Oso.
I'm sorry.
Really.
Good luck.
Call Miguel.
Let's see what he can do.
What's that?
Housekeeping?
Did you say our names?
- Uh. no.
- Did you mention the CIA
- in any way?
- What?
- Did you mention the CIA?
- No.
Look. they were in the
room when we got there.
- It would be very rude...
- It's fine. it's fine.
It's my fault. I should have warned you.
- What?
- Yeah. this is
a big account for Loba.
This is his way of ensuring
that we're never gonna take
our business anywhere else.
Whoa. whoa... What.
they bugged the room?
Also. I noticed
that the blinds are open.
so I hope you smiled
for the camera.
- Shit.
- You're still not grasping
who these people are. are you?
Look. nobody here's your
friend. nobody here's
ever doing anything nice
for you just because.
That's not how it works.
So. what. is this bad?
- It's probably fine.
- Yeah.
Unless you're planning
on running for President
in the future.
Okay. look. um...
uh. you might as well
finish up at this point.
Please be careful what you say.
Hey.
Was it everything you
dreamed it would be?
It was...
until I started thinking about the guy
on the other end of the telephoto.
Yeah.
I bet that probably works
better than thinking
- about baseball. doesn't it?
- I'm sorry.
I should have seen it coming.
Should have known better.
Thanks. can we do. um...
two tequilas?
Dos tequilas?
Expensive?
Thank you.
Your Spanish is really coming along.
Gracias.
Do you ever think...
in a million years. that we would be...
in Panama City together?
You incubating a nasty
case of Chlamydia...
While I broker
illegal international arms deals.
No. but I'm having a good time.
Feel like I'm back in the fight.
You know. probably you could get back
in the game officially...
if you wanted to.
I could probably even get you recruited
at this point.
No chance.
Right. I forgot. you got the whole...
skydiving racket to get back to.
- It's not a racket. Teddy.
- Tell Dad about it yet?
- Why?
- I was just curious how...
he took the news that you
had completely given up
on a life of service.
How do you think he took it?
You know what he said
to me when I told him
I was recruited by the CIA?
He said. "Oh. you mean those pussies
who sneak around alleys and
stab you in the back?"
I think you're too hard on him.
And I know he was tough
when we were kids. but...
at least he stuck around.
Yeah. I wish he hadn't.
The fuck?
- Take it back.
- Oh. fuck you. take it back.
- All I'm saying is if
that asshole had left. maybe
Mom would have stayed.
- Fuckin' bullshit.
- No. it's not.
- You romanticize her.
- No. I don't romanticize her.
- I don't blame her. It's different.
- Maybe you should.
I left as soon as I could. too.
You didn't have two small boys at home.
I got one small boy at home right now...
- I'm not there. am I?
- It's different.
- How is that different?
- You're in Paul's life.
You know where he is and how he is.
She just walked out on us.
Didn't even leave a note.
That's unforgivable.
and you know that.
To Mom and Dad.
Fuck 'em both.
Fuck them both.
Damn bills and shit...
Damn. I'm gonna have to put
a bell on you. Peanut.
- Franklin around?
- Nah. but you wanna leave
some cash for him. I'll take it.
You don't trust us or something?
- No. of course I do.
- So. what. you ain't got it?
It's nothing. I'll just...
just hang out. just wait for Franklin.
Oh. shit.
- You got jacked. huh?
- No. I... I didn't get jacked.
- Yeah. you did.
- No. it's just...
it's just. like. tied up right now.
- so I don't want to trouble you guys...
- Spit it out. Peanut.
My dad took it.
Yo daddy. who you live
with. took your cocaine?
Well. then take it back. boy.
Fuck wrong with you?
Hold... wait. hold on.
That's that. uh. house that Franklin
used to stay at. right?
Y'all make your little nasty movies.
I'm gonna help you out.
We gon' get that.
Hell yeah. I'm with that shit.
Mm-mm. you think I'm
letting you up there
with a bunch of white naked bitches?
Man. this about business.
You're not going to
no titty house. Leon.
Peaches. wanna go to the titty house?
Ey. Jerome.
- you need my help. right?
- I don't need
- a goddamn thing from you.
- What now?
Rob got jacked by his daddy.
What? How?
- What. y'all going up there?
- Hell. yeah.
- How much we talking?
- Like. two keys.
Fuck...
Hold up.
He knows me.
Pops know I'm the one fronting the shit?
Who driving?
- Leon. you coming?
- No.
Uh-uh!
'Sup with the spot?
Things have been a little
rough since Mom left.
What?
- When that happen?
- I don't know...
Couple months ago.
Ey. where yo pops at?
Back this way. They're shooting.
Ha. How y'all doin'?
Hey. cut it out.
Man. you should go get your dad.
Let's wait 'till they cut.
That's it. Hold that eye contact.
Hey!
He's really not gonna like this. man.
- It's all good.
- Nice.
Your pops always treated
me like family...
- Move to your left.
- It'll be all right.
That's so great. That's good.
And cut. That's great.
Jesus Christ. Rob. what the fuck?
Hey. where the bitches at?
There supposed to be titties!
Where the fucking titties
and the bitches?
- It's a gay one.
- A gay one.
Mr. Volpe.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Oh. Franklin.
It's great to see you. really.
but this isn't. uh. the best of times.
I think that Rob might
have explained that to you
before you came all the way out here.
- We need to talk. Dad.
- No.
No. we don't need to talk.
I'm burning daylight.
I need to shoot. is what I need to do.
and you need to get these fucking
- people out of here.
- With all due respect. sir.
from what I hear. you
may be financing this
with something that don't belong to you.
Ungrateful little shit.
The fuck you been telling them?
- Huh?
- Hey...
Don't fucking touch me.
Hey. everybody get the fuck out!
Now!
Don't do that. motherfucker.
Uh. we're all right.
We're all right.
Well. you guys just completely fucked up
my entire shoot. That's great.
I hope you're all really happy.
Franklin tell you about
all the time he spent
living here with us?
How we brought him into our home?
- How we looked after him?
- You know I appreciate
everything you and
Mrs. Volpe did for me.
Yeah. and I can really feel
the love right now. man.
You got any idea how
much food alone costs?
Huh? I mean you were a Shop-Vac.
You weren't as bad as Rob. though.
Guess how much it cost to raise Rob.
I got clothes. I got dental.
I... I got toys. I got trips.
You got any idea?
214 grand.
- That's fucked up.
- You give everything you can
to your children. and
what do you get back?
Not a goddamn thing in return.
Hey. Jim...
everything you're saying
right now is irrelevant.
You know Avi was my connect. right?
I mean. if it wasn't for me.
you wouldn't even be in
this goddamn business.
What I'm looking for
is a little fucking.
you know. gratitude.
Where is it?
Huh?
Where's my coke?
It's gone.
So. if I'm gonna be honest with you.
what I'm looking for is a little bit
- of my generosity to be repaid.
- Yeah. well. I wish I knew
your generosity had strings attached.
But I can see how hard
of a state you in.
I'm sorry about that.
How's a 50% family discount sound?
Man. my company is circling the drain.
I can't pay you half... I
can't pay you anything.
What?
- You didn't tell me that.
- Why the fuck
would I tell you that? What.
are you gonna bail me out?
Huh? All you ever done is take.
That's all you've ever
done. take. take...
Hey. hey! You stop
squirming. motherfucker.
Now look. you done took from us.
you done stole from your goddamn kid.
Ey. come here. Opie. Come here.
Get your ass over here.
- Slap yo daddy.
- Oh...
Slap yo motherfucking daddy.
Motherfucker gon' steal from you.
make you pay him back for raising you?
Smack yo goddamn daddy.
Go on. man. smack him!
Oh. come on. man. you
can do better than that.
Smack yo goddamn daddy!
Yeah!
Let me show you how to
smack this motherfucker.
You gon' give back everything you took.
That's how you smack. You gon' give back
- every fucking thing you took!
- Don't hurt him. come on!
Come on!
- It's on me!
- Want more?
- It's on me. I'll own it!
- Why you even care
about this deadbeat?
Because he's my dad. okay?
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of it.
Hey. we still gon'
take something. right?
Nah.
Rob's good for it.
Let's go.
- Hey. Lorena. you copy?
- Yeah. I'm here.
Walker and Dobbs are about
to tap in. you good?
- Need anything?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Go ahead. over.
Copy. Over and out.
Still nothing?
I'd be a lot less calm if there were.
Still no word from Lucia?
You need to relax.
- This is a mistake.
- They'll come back eventually.
I'm not talking about the suppliers.
I mean not arresting Lucia
when you had the chance.
- She's not going anywhere.
- How do you know that?
She could be crossing
the border right now.
She can't run.
Not until she makes shit
right with La Fuerza.
Gets that green light off her head.
And even if she did. we'd find her.
I just don't understand this.
You have her for
trafficking. distribution.
for fucking murder...
what else do you want?
What are we doing here waiting
for these fucking guerros?
I told you when you first came to us
that if you did what we asked
we'd get you what you wanted.
and we will.
She's gonna suffer in prison
for a long. long time.
But right now. I need you
to shut the fuck up...
and get on my page.
Hey.
Hey. Franklin!
Mike Cho. meet Nia Jones.
- Pleased to meet you.
Place is filthy. Cho. come on.
Broom's right there.
Franklin tell you he used to work here?
- No!
- From what I hear.
you keeping the job in the family.
She got paperwork for you.
How'd you know to come here?
Your son has some pull
in the neighborhood.
Yeah. shit's time sensitive.
so I should get to it.
Cho.
When the hell you get a hot dog machine?
Like it?
- You make money off this?
- Yes. we do.
What's goin' on?
I'll reach out when I
hear back from them.
Thank you again.
For everything.
I'm proud of you.
You're doing real good.
I hope you know that.
Don't leave Moms out to dry.
- Want one?
- Nah.
Don't know why you changed your mind.
but I'm happy you did.
He's supposed to be real good.
Handles cases like
this one all the time.
I've already paid his retainer.
so he's expecting your call.
So you always go out hunting
after all your cases like this?
No. actually.
Your pops has a very special place
in my heart.
- My father was a Panther.
- For real?
- Why they threw me his case.
- Damn. that's crazy.
Where is he now. your dad?
He died when I was 12.
Got shot during some robbery.
- At least that's what they said.
- Sorry to hear that.
- So you from up North?
- Nah. here.
- Baldwin Hills.
- Where'd you go to school?
- Crenshaw?
- Our Holy Mother.
You know Dizzy?
Oh. Dizzy was
my sixth-grade boyfriend.
- Oh. man.
- 'Till he dropped me
- for Vonkeisha Jackson.
- Oh. she was a ho.
- Right?
- Damn.
- You do college?
- Went to Middlebury
for a minute on scholarship.
Don't tell me. you was
the only black person
- in there. right?
- There were three of us.
But I left after a couple of
years. ended up at Howard.
- That was more my style.
- Now you're back
- for good. huh?
- Mm-mm.
Saving up for law school.
Law school.
Can't change the system
from the outside.
No. you can't.
Can I take you out sometime?
Dinner. maybe?
- A drink?
- I don't think so.
Look. I get why you hustle.
and I see what you want.
but I've been there before.
and I don't wanna go back.
I'll be seeing you. Franklin.
What are you feeling for dinner?
Whatever.
Burgers? Hmm.
Nah. not burgers.
So. then. not whatever.
- Hey. man. office...
- Don't look at it.
Just keep your eyes straight ahead.
What?
You're 100% certain you
didn't say anything
about who we really are at the hotel?
To the hookers?
Yeah. I'm completely sure.
Why?
Somebody's watching the office.
They just went past.
might have made my car.
I've got eyes on them. I'm following.
Copy that. We're
southbound on Arlington.
Good. gun it.
We'll pin them at Imperial.
Copy that. here we go.
And we have a tail.
I'm gonna try to avoid congestion.
- Just keep an eye on our front.
- What am I looking for?
Anybody trying to box us in.
like a van stopping suddenly.
- people jumping out.
- What is this. like.
some sort or cartel hit squad?
Jesus Christ.
Teddy. talk to me. what do you see?
There's two cars now.
Leap-frogging. It's
gotta be the... the Feds.
Is your vision still 20-20?
Why? What am I looking for?
There's a blue Chevy Caprice
about five lanes back.
I'm gonna try to pull
them in close enough
for you to read the plates.
- Two occupants?
- Yep. that's it.
- Here. let me know when you got it.
- I got it.
- Okay.
- Hold on!
What the hell is going on?
I don't know.
Uh. uh. uh.
I done already told y'all.
quit running around my
house with that bottle.
Y'all gone get this
shit all on the sofa.
Sit your ass down and be quiet.
Hey. hey. hey.
What's going on. muppets?
Who's hungry? Come on. come get it.
- Here. take that.
- Hey. baby.
Thank you.
Hey. little mama.
- Say "hey."
- Hey.
- Will you cut it out...
- I got something for you.
Ooh.
- We like that.
- Diapers and formula.
I wanna see her in her new clothes.
- you hear me?
- Thank you. baby brother.
If this is Deandre. I'm
gonna be really mad.
Tch. Shut up.
Hey.
- You remember us?
- Do I remember?
Is that shit supposed to be funny?
- Need to talk to you.
- About what?
- Who is that?
- Oh. it's just some friends
for business. you know what I'm saying?
Hey. make sure they
don't eat all my food.
Please? Thank you.
You must either be stupid
or out your goddamn mind
coming to my neighborhood
at this time of night.
We have something for you.
It needed to be discussed in private.
and it couldn't wait.
Wanna know who killed your friends?
We can take you right to him.
Show you where to get at him and how.
And why would you do that?
'Cause you're gonna tell us
how to cook up that rock.
Why would I do that?
That recipe's going to
get out sooner or later.
At least this way you
get something in return
when it does.
That don't sound like
an even trade to me.
No?
What else do you want?
I have access to pure cocaine.
Straight off the boat. affordable.
Smart man like you?
No reason you shouldn't be running
your own operation. if
that's what you want.
There's enough room in
this game for all of us.
- Mmm.
- We can make sure
you and your family are
well taken care of.
and obviously nobody would ever know
this conversation ever took place.
It's my pager and my office.
I look forward to hearing from you soon.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-